Chris Esterhuizen

Electronic Engineering Student

0729271203

cesterhuizenes@gmail.com

• 176 Brooks Street, Brooklyn, Pretoria

Birthday: 03-04-97 ID: 9704035053089

Objective

I am a 23-year old enterprising fourth year undergraduate electronic engineering student at the University of Pretoria intending to develop as an intern. In terms of results and objectives; I am a structured, pragmatic worker looking to broaden my knowledge of the industry. As a starting fourth year student, I have an adequate understanding of electronic engineering theory and design, testing instrumentation and programming.

Education

BEng Electronic Engineering | University of Pretoria

JAN 2016 - PRESENT

Relevant course work:

Control Systems

Microprocessors

Electromagnetism

Microwaves and antennas

Analogue electronics

Linear Systems

Imperative Programming

Digital Signal Processing

Automation

National Senior Certificate | High School

2011 - 2015

I attended Helpmekaar Kollege Private school in Johannesburg and attained my IEB Level 7 matric Certificate with 5 distinctions.

SAT: College admission board exams, United States of America 2014.

Awards

Golden Key Member 2019

University of Pretoria Engineers Without Borders project of the year, 2017: Implementing a drainage system for Kutumela Molefi Farm School.

Eskom International Science Expo category winner and winner of the Department of science and Arts medal for outstanding achievement 2014

Working and Programming Skills

- Strong technical working skills
- MATLAB
- Python
- C and C++
- Java
- MS Excel
- Verilog Hardware Description language (VHDL)
- Circuit Simulation software LTSpice
- Lates
- Assembly

Languages

- English
- Afrikaans

Other Skills

- Code 08 (C08) drivers license with own vehicle
- First aid level 1 & 2 diploma certificate – Cal med First Aid Training (obtained 2016)

Relevant Experience

- Electrical Engineering Apprentice at Consolidated Power Engineering (2018-2020)
- EBIT House committee member in the Faculty of Electronic, Electrical and Computer Engineering (2016-2018)